um
okay guys
welcome back to nicole tv
we have a lot to catch up on
i'm really just making this video to let
you guys know i have officially been
rewarded with the best sea award
yay give it up for me
[Music]
it's true
i just want to say
um
it feels
natural it feels normal
i don't teach any classes i don't have a
little you know
of link but if you girls would like to
learn no i'm just kidding
tokyo vanity sent me that so if you
don't know who that is
look it up
and check her out
she's a rapper
and she got some good music so
what if i get flagged
this says collect call
2021 best award kevin nicole
now she awarded me with that last year
but
i did not see it until this year because
you can see we got our house remodeled
and i was in the room where i just used
to throw [\h__\h] and put fan mail and
by the way my p.o box is closed so don't
say nothing i was going through it and
she has sent that so i found a song
collect
it's called collect call
[Music]
but anyways shout out to talk for
sending me that
this room that i'm in used to be
i'm gonna insert a picture or a video
this room
and now it's my content room
so
what we're really here for today
is the clothing hawk
wait hello y'all bear with me
vegan eyebrow
not a clothing haul but
i mean
i guess i could call it a product review
i ordered some stuff from
s
h e i n
i don't know how y'all pronounce it i'd
be like sheen
washing
somebody said she in she out
and somebody else said shane
i don't know
she
so for the girls i was a little
skeptical because
i was a little skeptical because
because
i was a little skeptical because how did
i do that
i was gonna skeptical
anyways when i was hearing about sheen i
was saying
y'all say bad stuff
so i don't want to order no clothes
but
i still found some cute things that i
liked i didn't know what to get like it
was confusing on the website
i just got what i thought was nice
i'm gonna take them out of the bag
i don't wanna miss my room
where should i pour it out
okay
anyway
a bunch of cute
earrings
these are supposed to go with
this shirt
so i got one shirt a bunch of
accessories and i got this furry purse
because i actually have some heels like
this and i have some arm cuffs and i'm
gonna put that outfit on at the end to
show y'all what they're supposed to look
like please don't screenshot it it's a
little tacky i'm just trying to show
y'all
it's not a fashion show
maybe the yellow light messing up my
quality i don't know i hope not
because i did a video on so long
it's been almost a year
yeah
[Music]
we got a lot to talk about
youtube here
although my nails dirty so i'm doing
like this and stuff like this youtube
take these out
sweet mother of pearl
and i got him pearls is my ponytail mess
up
okay
i guess i'll show them all to y'all
then try them
[Music]
or should i show them as i go
whatever
here are some cards
this reminded me of art like
y'all gonna drag me if i say this
i forgot the first name but van gogh
robert van gaal
mona lisa
ice cubes because i eat ice a lot
grapes
hoops with the pearls
chicken wing necklace
it wasn't supposed to be so big but
we're gonna get into that later
where the [\h__\h]
no damn product in it
oh
okay
so this is the thing i ordered from my
nose
anklet
oh my god the popcorn
cherries
okay this is the shirt
that i ordered
i guess i'll try that on on camera
it's supposed to go with those earrings
so
anything nice
should i actually put my phone right
here
so i can just be in the chair and the
camera in my face
i'm trying to get used to my new room
y'all normally i just sit on the floor
camera propped up but anyways i'll get
my hair done tomorrow for mother's day
and i have an event i was supposed to be
in new york
unfortunately i cannot make it because
i'm not vaccinated i'll be working from
home
oh my gosh look
what y'all think
ice ice baby
so
yeah these are my favorite all of them
are my favorite actually
and
they're bigger than they look in the
picture
a few items are bigger than they seemed
in the picture
but actually
i think i like that
okay sheen
sheen
shane
girl
noodles
let me tell y'all i was looking for a
noodle shirt because i wanted to wear
these earrings with a shirt that said
send nudes i'm still going to try to
find a shirt like that and if i can't
find one because i went all on amazon if
i can't find one
i'll just make one
here's the noodles wait my sideburns
because i'm not doing my hair
y'all know that
oh my god it's nasty
and you would do it too if you didn't
give them [\h__\h] noodles
i don't have my shirt like i won't but
so i went ahead and i took everything i
could pack that way ain't got to be open
and close up and close i'm going to
close because that's going to take up
too much time i want to get in your way
and ripped all day
even though you been begging for me to
get back on youtube
cause y'all been bored i've been bored
too it's not nothing to watch on here
but anyways
popcorn
y'all i had to give me some starbucks
not that i'm a huge fan i'm not one of
those girls i just go every morning and
give me a hot chocolate extra creamy
extra sugar extra vanilla
oh my god the popcorns
i hate that i stay by the airport shut
them
oh my god look at the popcorn
wait my
ain't him
damn
wait
hello
hi this is the delivery team with
appliances for less just calling to let
you know that we're on our way we'll be
there in about 35 minutes
okay all right we'll see you soon all
right thank you all right bye bye
[Music]
okay don't be too loud
stop stopping
fat ass
there you go
how y'all feeling about the popcorn
ugh why do i feel like my camera need to
be up
i don't think y'all in my face
oh [\h__\h]
damn
i almost failed
i like the popcorn
[Music]
anyways i love the popcorn
ew
10 out of 10.
they are so pretty
cherries
oh i have to find a popcorn shirt to go
with the popcorns
cherries
i have a cherry dress
grapes
great
i don't want to wear a grape shirt
though i feel like this too much
oh come out my ear
come out my ear
come on my ear
grapes
had to make sure it was still recording
cause y'all when i went and i got my hot
chocolate why the [\h__\h] i went to the
back of my phone and it was off
my storage full
i paid 9.99 a month for two terabytes my
store should not be full
the store is not stored in the way it's
supposed to and i deleted all 16 000 of
my photos
the problem is not me
here are the cards
i hope you all like them
do i like them
i think i i want to see the card when i
face forward so hopefully you can see
the print when i turn my head
caleb huh
now you can see the card in the front
kayla huh
hey girl
so yeah these aren't one of my favorites
but i still like them because they're
unique they were actually a lot smaller
too
i think i prefer these to be a little
bit smaller
lollipops
lollipop lollipop bally lollipop
lollipop lollipop i don't really like
those because they're way bigger than
they were supposed to be and i prefer
those to be a little bit tinier
here's a pack of suckers
i won't try on all of them because you
get the [\h__\h] points try the yellow
ones on since i have them yellow wow
they look delicious
i like the suckers
don't move by the airport y'all
now these also were actually smaller but
it's whatever well no no it's not
whatever the [\h__\h] i prefer those to be
smaller like how they were like some of
them do need to be like fun size little
little
i like them because that's what i chose
a lot of these products for the cuteness
and like the size
this [\h__\h] heavy as hell
why and these was supposed to be way sm
damn
uh
definitely not feeling the strawberries
not cause they ugly but cause they heavy
ow my ear hot
chicken wing necklace
not gonna put it on you get a picture
this was also supposed to be smaller
i think i prefer it smaller
fake nose piercing
what y'all think
wait i just thought of a look i'm gonna
put my starry night earrings in
with the nose ring
i dropped it in my heart i had a heart
attack
it didn't break though thank god you
know why
art is expensive
was that corny i don't care fine i'm a
mom so
at times i will be corny and y'all can
tell me that i have to try on the shirt
okay so here's the shirt with the
earrings
but do y'all see the look i was going
for
like since it gave art it was an art
shirt all right me neither moving on
uh
that's all the earrings
oh my god
this one is cute
[\h__\h] it who pearls i'm trying to go fast
y'all
hell yeah
it's giving
i don't know but you get the picture
a picture says a thousand words so y'all
tell me what it's giving it's getting
grown sexy
oh here's a set
look how pretty these diamonds look
though
you see that this a necklace
airplane shut up already which way am i
supposed to [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
turn the right way donuts
oh yeah hell yeah johnny dying icebox
said the jeweler
damn it damn
[Music]
dancing
if you're walking in the mall
and that little boy with the messy hair
come up to you with the um camera and be
like
diamond tester don't run don't freeze
don't panic
you stand up proudly and say
she ain't collaborated with icebox
because here we are they look cute they
look real
who gives a [\h__\h] this is an anklet
oh yeah what if i broke my shelf
then i would have cried the [\h__\h] so
anyways you get the picture that's how
it's supposed to look
and here's the other one
wham i've never used my backs to my
earrings
maybe i should start
done see y'all next time